Register of the William Patrick Clark papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- United States Department of State File, 1981-1982
  - Alphabetical correspondence, 1981
    - Donlon, Sean (Irish ambassador) (Box-folder 27: 12)
    - Drury, Allen (Box-folder 27: 13)
    - E (Box-folder 27: 14)
    - Elekdag, Sukru (Turkish ambassador) (Box-folder 27: 15)
    - Ellingwood, Herbert E. (Box-folder 27: 16)
    - Evron, Ephraim (Israeli ambassador) (Box-folder 27: 17)
    - F (Box-folder 28: 1)
    - Feinstein, Dianne (Box-folder 28: 2)
    - Feulner, Edwin J., Jr. (Box-folder 28: 3)
    - Figueres, Jose (president of Costa Rica) (Box-folder 28: 4)
    - Finch, Robert H. (Box-folder 28: 5)
    - Findley, Paul (Box-folder 28: 6)
    - Fish, Hamilton (Box-folder 28: 7)
    - G (Box-folder 28: 8)
    - Garrick, Robert M. (Box-folder 28: 9)
    - Gavin, John (Box-folder 28: 10)
    - Ghorbal, Ashraf A. (Egyptian ambassador) (Box-folder 28: 11)
    - Gish, Theodore G. (Box-folder 28: 12)
    - Goldberg, Arthur J. (Box-folder 28: 13)
    - Greene, Joseph N., Jr. (Box-folder 28: 14)
    - H (Box-folder 28: 15-16)
    - Harman, Phillip (Box-folder 28: 17)
    - Harmer, John L. (Box-folder 29: 1)
    - Hatch, Orrin G. (Box-folder 29: 2)
    - Hayakawa, S. I. (Box-folder 29: 3)
    - Helms, Jesse (Box-folder 29: 4)
    - Henderson, Sir Nicholas (British ambassador) (Box-folder 29: 5)
    - I (Box-folder 29: 6)
    - J (Box-folder 29: 7)
    - James, E. Pendleton (Box-folder 29: 8)
    - Jones, Peter T. (Box-folder 29: 9)
    - K (Box-folder 29: 10)
    - Kampelman, Max M. (Box-folder 29: 11)
    - Kane, Robert F. (Box-folder 29: 12)
    - Kelly, Michael J. (Box-folder 29: 13)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. (Box-folder 29: 14)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J. (Box-folder 29: 15)
    - Korologos, Tom C. (Box-folder 29: 16)
    - L (Box-folder 29: 17)
    - Lagomarsino, Robert J. (Box-folder 30: 1)
    - Lane, L. W., Jr. (Box-folder 30: 2)
    - Laxalt, Paul (Box-folder 30: 3)
    - Lefever, Ernest W. (Box-folder 30: 4)
    - Lenczowski, George (Box-folder 30: 5)
    - Lewis, Drew (Box-folder 30: 6)
    - Lillie, Mildred (Box-folder 30: 7)
    - Lord, Winston (Box-folder 30: 8)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe (Box-folder 30: 9)
    - Luce, Gordon C. (Box-folder 30: 10)
    - M (Box-folder 30: 11-13)
    - McCormack, Richard (Box-folder 30: 14)
    - McDonald, Larry P. (Box-folder 30: 15)
    - Mosk, Stanley (Box-folder 30: 16)
    - N (Box-folder 31: 1)
    - Neumann, Robert G. (Box-folder 31: 2)
    - O (Box-folder 31: 3)
    - P (Box-folder 31: 4)
    - Padilla, Hernan (Box-folder 31: 5)
    - Percy, Charles H. (Box-folder 31: 6)
    - Posner, Gerald L. (Box-folder 31: 7)
    - Pustay, John S. (Box-folder 31: 8)
    - Q (Box-folder 31: 9)
    - Quinn, Arthur Lewis (Box-folder 31: 10)
    - R (Box-folder 31: 11, Box-folder 32: 1)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 32: 2)
    - Reilly, Robert R. (Box-folder 32: 3)
    - Richardson, Frank K. (Box-folder 32: 4)
    - Robinson, Gilbert A. (Box-folder 32: 5)
    - Rostropovich, Mstislav (Box-folder 32: 6)
    - S (Box-folder 32: 7-9)
    - Schober, Karl Herbert (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 32: 10)
    - Shackley, Theodore G. (Box-folder 32: 11)
    - Shakespeare, Frank (Box-folder 32: 12)
    - Sinatra, Frank (Box-folder 32: 13)
    - Smith, William French (Box-folder 32: 14)
    - Stevens, Ted (Box-folder 32: 15)
    - Stewart, Potter (Box-folder 32: 16)
    - T (Box-folder 33: 1)
    - Tambs, Lewis A. (Box-folder 33: 2)
    - Thompson, W. Scott (Box-folder 33: 3)
    - U (Box-folder 33: 4)
    - V (Box-folder 33: 5)
    - Von Damm, Helene (Box-folder 33: 6)
    - W (Box-folder 33: 7-8)
    - Webster, William H. (Box-folder 33: 9)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 33: 10)
    - Wick, Charles Z. (Box-folder 33: 11)
    - Y (Box-folder 33: 12)
    - Z (Box-folder 33: 13)
  - Subject file
    - Forgery, 1982 (Box-folder 33: 14)
      Memoranda relating to forged signature of Clark on document distributed to Greek newspapers
    - Pacific Forum, 1981 (Box-folder 33: 15)
      Background paper for symposium on National Threat Perceptions in East Asia/Pacific
  - Clippings and serial issues, 1981 (Box-folder 34: 1-3, Box-folder 33: 16)
  - Travel vouchers (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - Resignation as Deputy Secretary, 1982 (Box-folder 34: 6)
- United States National Security Council File, 1982-1983
  Papers of William P. Clark as National Security Adviser to President Ronald Reagan, 1982-1983
  - Appointment as National Security Adviser, 1982
    - General (Box-folder 35: 1)
      Announcement and press conference transcript
    - Congratulatory letters (Box-folder 35: 2)
    - Press coverage (Box-folder 35: 3-4)
  - Biographical file
    - General (Box-folder 35: 5)
      Press releases and biographical articles
    - Press coverage (Box-folder 36: 1, Box-folder 35: 6-7)
  - Appointment books
    - 1982 (Box-folder 36: 2)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 36: 3)
  - Schedules
    - 1982 January-February (Box-folder 36: 4)
    - 1982 March-April (Box-folder 36: 5)
    - 1982 May-June (Box-folder 36: 6)
    - 1982 July-August (Box-folder 37: 1)
    - 1982 September-October (Box-folder 37: 2)
    - 1982 November-December (Box-folder 37: 3)
    - 1983 January-February (Box-folder 37: 4)
    - 1983 March-April (Box-folder 37: 5)
    - 1983 May-June (Box-folder 37: 6)
    - 1983 July-August (Box-folder 38: 1)
    - 1983 September-November (Box-folder 38: 2)
  - Speeches and events file
    Correspondence, memoranda, notes, speeches, travel vouchers and press coverage
    - Meeting with President Hosni Mubarak of Egypt, Washington, D.C., 1982 February 3 (Box-folder 38: 3)
    - Briefing (nature of event unclear), 1982 February 4 (Box-folder 38: 4)
    - Visit to California to brief former President Richard M. Nixon, 1982 February 22 (Box-folder 38: 5)
    - Visit to Georgia to brief former President Jimmy Carter, 1982 March 3-8 (Box-folder 38: 6)
    - Afghanistan Day proclamation, White House, 1982 March 10 (Box-folder 38: 7)
    - California Cattlemen's Association visit to White House, 1982 March 17 (Box-folder 38: 8)
    - Friendly Sons of St. Patrick banquet, Los Angeles, California, 1982 March 17 (Box-folder 38: 9)
    - Agricultural Leadership Forum, Visalia, California, 1982 March 18 (Box-folder 38: 10)
    - Visit to Jamaica and Barbados with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 April 7-9 (Box-folder 38: 11)
    - Visit to California to brief former President Gerald R. Ford, 1982 April 28-May 2 (Box-folder 38: 12)
    - Foreign Service Day luncheon, Department of State, 1982 May 7 (Box-folder 38: 13)
    - Visit to Illinois with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 May 9-10 (Box-folder 38: 14)
    - Center for International and Strategic Studies, Georgetown University, meeting, 1982 May 21 (Box-folder 39: 1)
    - Visit to California with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 May 25-30 (Box-folder 39: 2)
    - Economic Summit visit to France, Italy, Great Britain and West Germany with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 June 2-11 (Box-folder 39: 3)
    - Council of the Americas conference, Department of State, 1982 June 21 (Box-folder 39: 4)
    - Visit to California with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 July 1-11 (Box-folder 39: 5)
    - Visit to Iowa and Connecticut with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 August 2-3 (Box-folder 39: 6)
    - American Bar Association dinner, San Francisco, California, 1982 August 7 (Box-folder 39: 7)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars convention, Los Angeles, California, 1982 August 16 (Box-folder 39: 8)
    - Visit to California with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 August 20-September 7 (Box-folder 39: 9)
    - Visit to Nebraska and Utah with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 September 9-10 (Box-folder 39: 10)
    - Visit to Mexico, 1982 September 15-18 (Box-folder 39: 11)
    - Quadrangular Conference, Center for International and Strategic Studies, Georgetown University, 1982 September 21 (Box-folder 39: 12)
    - Symposium on the 15th anniversary of the Outer Space Treaty, National Academy of Sciences, 1982 September 23 (Box-folder 39: 13)
    - Coalition for Peace through Strength Congressional Advisory Board meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 September 30 (Box-folder 39: 14)
    - Visit to Mexico and California with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 October 7-11 (Box-folder 39: 15)
    - Defense Science Board dinner, Arlington, Virginia, 1982 October 14 (Box-folder 39: 16)
    - Videotape session for salute to Gordon Schaber, 1982 October 18 (Box-folder 39: 17)
    - Visit to Illinois and Nebraska with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 October 20-21 (Box-folder 39: 18)
    - Visit to France to meet President Francois Mitterrand, 1982 October 26-28 (Box-folder 40: 1)
    - Chamber of Commerce luncheon, San Diego, California, 1982 October 29 (Box-folder 40: 2)
    - 1972 Presidential Advance Team reunion, Washington, D.C., 1982 November 6 (Box-folder 40: 3)
    - President's Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1982 November 10 (Box-folder 40: 4)
    - President's Commission on Executive Exchange meeting, Department of State, 1982 November 10 (Box-folder 40: 5)
    - Ronald Reagan radio address, 1982 November 13 (Box-folder 40: 6)
      Includes draft remarks
    - Visit to California with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 November 23-29 (Box-folder 40: 7)
    - Visit to Brazil, Colombia, Costa Rica and Honduras with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 November 30-December 4 (Box-folder 40: 8)
    - Heritage Foundation conference, Washington, D.C. (canceled), 1982 December 9 (Box-folder 40: 9)
      Includes proposed speech
    - President's National Security Telecommunications Advisory Committee meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 December 14 (Box-folder 40: 10)
    - Visit to California with President Ronald Reagan, 1982 December 23-1983 January 2 (Box-folder 40: 11)
    - Visit to Illinois with President Ronald Reagan (canceled), 1983 January 19-20 (Box-folder 40: 12)
    - Mid-term press briefing, Washington, D.C., 1983 January 20 (Box-folder 40: 13)
      Includes talking points
    - Visit to defense bases in Mississippi and Louisiana with Secretary of Defense Caspar Weinberger, 1983 January 22-23 (Box-folder 40: 14)
    - State of the Union press background briefing, Washington, D.C., 1983 January 25 (Box-folder 40: 15)
    - National League of Families meeting, Crystal City, Virginia, 1983 January 27 (Box-folder 40: 16)
    - Visit to Austria and West Germany, 1983 February 8-13 (Box-folder 40: 17)
    - Wehrkunde Conference, Munich, West Germany, 1983 February 12 (Box-folder 40: 18)
    - U.S.-Jamaica Business Committee meeting, New York, New York, 1983 February 22 (Box-folder 40: 19)
    - Visit to California with President Ronald Reagan in conjunction with visit of Queen Elizabeth II, 1983 February 28-March 6 (Box-folder 41: 1)
    - Charro del Ano award, Los Angeles, California, 1983 March 5 (Box-folder 41: 2)
    - American Newspaper Publishers Association meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 March 8 (Box-folder 41: 3)
    - Lincoln Club of Northern California dinner, Napa, California, 1983 March 11 (Box-folder 41: 4)
    - Friendly Sons of St. Patrick banquet, Washington, D.C., 1983 March 17 (Box-folder 41: 5)
    - Republican Congressional Leadership Council meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 March 21 (Box-folder 41: 6)
    - Briefings on speech by President Ronald Reagan, White House, 1983 March 24 (Box-folder 41: 7)
    - Republican National Committee Executive Committee meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 March 25 (Box-folder 41: 8)
    - Visit to California with President Ronald Reagan, 1983 March 30-April 3 (Box-folder 41: 9)
    - Evans-Novak Political Forum, Washington, D.C., 1983 April 7 (Box-folder 41: 10)
    - Visit to Venezuela and Brazil, 1983 April 8-10 (Box-folder 41: 11)
    - National Cattlemen's Association meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 April 16 (Box-folder 41: 12)
    - Republican Senatorial Trust Committee meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 April 20 (Box-folder 41: 13)
    - President's Key Supporters briefing, White House, 1983 April 20 (Box-folder 41: 14)
    - California Agricultural Leadership Program meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 April 21 (Box-folder 41: 15)
    - Interview with U.S. News and World Report, 1983 May (Box-folder 41: 16)
      Includes printed transcript
    - Citizens for the Republic Ronald Reagan Award, Los Angeles, California, 1983 May 5 (Box-folder 42: 1-2)
    - Central American Conference, Washington, D.C., 1983 May 12 (Box-folder 42: 3)
    - Pepperdine University commencement, California, 1983 May 14 (Box-folder 42: 4)
      Includes commencement address
    - Swearing-in of Helene Von Damm as U.S. ambassador to Austria, White House, 1983 May 16 (Box-folder 42: 5)
    - Capitol Hill Club Headliner breakfast, Washington, D.C., 1983 May 18 (Box-folder 42: 6)
    - President's Key Supporters briefing, White House, 1983 May 18 (Box-folder 42: 7)
    - Outreach Working Group on Central America meeting, White House, 1983 May 18 (Box-folder 42: 8)
    - Western Regional Council briefing, White House, 1983 May 18 (Box-folder 42: 9)
    - Visit to New York to brief former President Richard M. Nixon, 1983 May 26 (Box-folder 42: 10)
    - President's Economic Summit, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1983 May 27-31 (Box-folder 42: 11)
    - Dinner in honor of Clark, New York, New York, 1983 June 13 (Box-folder 42: 12)
    - European journalists briefing, Washington, D.C., 1983 June 22 (Box-folder 42: 13)
    - Freedom Federation briefing, Washington, D.C., 1983 June 22 (Box-folder 42: 14)
    - President's Key Supporters briefing, White House, 1983 June 24 (Box-folder 42: 15)
    - Indian-American leaders briefing, White House, 1983 June 24 (Box-folder 42: 16)
    - Visit to Kentucky, Kansas and California with President Ronald Reagan, 1983 June 29-July 5 (Box-folder 42: 17)
    - Visit to Florida with President Ronald Reagan, 1983 July 18 (Box-folder 42: 18)
    - Citizens for America briefing, White House, 1983 August 3 (Box-folder 42: 19)
    - Republican Congressional luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1983 August 3 (Box-folder 42: 20)
    - Washington area executives briefing on armament program, White House, 1983 August 4 (Box-folder 42: 21)
    - National Bipartisan Commission on Central America meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 August 11 (Box-folder 42: 22)
    - Visit to Florida, Texas, Louisiana, California and Washington with President Ronald Reagan, 1983 August 12-September 5 (Box-folder 42: 23)
    - Air Force Association convention, Washington, D.C., 1983 September 14 (Box-folder 43: 1)
    - German-American Tricentennial dinner, Anaheim, California, 1983 September 15 (Box-folder 43: 2)
    - American Bar Association briefing, Washington, D.C., 1983 September 21 (Box-folder 43: 3)
    - Visit to Williamsburg and Newport News, Virginia, 1983 September 23-24 (Box-folder 43: 4)
    - Visit to United Nations General Assembly with President Ronald Reagan, New York, New York, 1983 September 25-26 (Box-folder 43: 5)
    - Visit to West Germany, Austria and Italy, 1983 September 30-October 3 (Box-folder 43: 6)
    - Business Council meeting, Hot Springs, Virginia, 1983 October 7 (Box-folder 43: 7)
    - Christening of U.S.S. Henry M. Jackson, 1983 October 15 (Box-folder 43: 8)
    - Swearing-in of Nicholas M. Salgo as U.S. ambassador to Hungary, White House, 1983 October 24 (Box-folder 43: 9)
    - Council for National Policy dinner in honor of Clark, Washington, D.C., 1983 November 10 (Box-folder 43: 10)
  - Chronological correspondence (outgoing letters)
    - 1982 January (Box-folder 43: 11-12)
    - 1982 February (Box-folder 43: 13)
    - 1982 March (Box-folder 44: 1)
    - 1982 April (Box-folder 44: 2)
    - 1982 May (Box-folder 44: 3)
    - 1982 June (Box-folder 44: 4)
    - 1982 July (Box-folder 44: 5)
    - 1982 August (Box-folder 44: 6)
    - 1982 September (Box-folder 44: 7)
    - 1982 October (Box-folder 44: 8)
    - 1982 November (Box-folder 45: 1)
    - 1982 December (Box-folder 45: 2)
    - 1982 Christmas gift acknowledgments (Box-folder 45: 3)
    - 1983 January (Box-folder 45: 4)
    - 1983 February (Box-folder 45: 5)
    - 1983 March (Box-folder 45: 6)
    - 1983 April (Box-folder 45: 7)
    - 1983 May (Box-folder 45: 8)
    - 1983 June (Box-folder 45: 9)
    - 1983 July (Box-folder 46: 1)
    - 1983 August (Box-folder 46: 2)
    - 1983 September (Box-folder 46: 3)
    - 1983 October (Box-folder 46: 4)
    - 1983 November (Box-folder 46: 5)
  - 1982 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 46: 6)
    - Abrams, Elliott (Box-folder 47: 1)
    - Abshire, David M. (Box-folder 47: 2)
    - Allen, Richard V. (Box-folder 47: 3)
    - Anderson, Martin (Box-folder 47: 4)
    - Armstrong, Anne (Box-folder 47: 5)
    - B (Box-folder 47: 6-9)
    - Baez, Joan (Box-folder 48: 1)
    - Baker, James A., III (Box-folder 48: 2)
    - Barbarito, Luigi (papal nuncio) (Box-folder 48: 3)
    - Bea, Carlos (Box-folder 48: 4)
    - Bengelloun, Ali (Moroccan ambassador) (Box-folder 48: 5)
    - Bertain, Joseph, Jr. (Box-folder 48: 6)
    - Blinken, M. H. (Box-folder 48: 7)
    - Botha, R. F. (South African foreign minister) (Box-folder 48: 8)
    - Brooks, Claudia (Box-folder 48: 9)
    - Bruinsma, Theo. A. (Box-folder 48: 10)
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew (Box-folder 48: 11)
    - Buckley, James L. (Box-folder 48: 12)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr. (Box-folder 48: 13)
    - Burns, Arthur F. (Box-folder 48: 14)
    - C (Box-folder 48: 15-17)
    - Carrington, Lord Peter (British foreign secretary) (Box-folder 49: 1)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box-folder 49: 2)
    - Casey, William J. (Box-folder 49: 3)
    - Casmir, Fred L. (Box-folder 49: 4)
    - Chai, Zemin (Chinese ambassador) (Box-folder 49: 5)
    - Chennault, Anna (Box-folder 49: 6)
    - Cherne, Leo (Box-folder 49: 7)
    - Clark, Dick (Box-folder 49: 8)
    - Clarke, Bruce C. (Box-folder 49: 9)
    - Conde, Mamady Lamine (Guinean ambassador) (Box-folder 49: 10)
    - Conrad, Charles J. (Box-folder 49: 11)
    - Crane, Kent (Box-folder 49: 12)
    - Crane, Robert D. (Box-folder 49: 13)
    - Crozier, Brian (Box-folder 49: 14)
    - D (Box-folder 49: 15-16)
    - D'Amato, Alfonse M. (Box-folder 49: 17)
    - Dart, Justin (Box-folder 49: 18)
    - Davis, Jeffrey C. (Box-folder 49: 19)
    - DeLutis, Donald C. (Box-folder 49: 20)
    - Denton, Jeremiah (Box-folder 49: 21)
    - Ditchley Foundations (Box-folder 49: 22)
    - Dolan, Anthony R. (Box-folder 49: 23)
    - Dole, Robert (Box-folder 49: 24)
    - Dooge, James (Irish foreign minister) (Box-folder 49: 25)
    - Drury, Allen (Box-folder 49: 26)
    - E (Box-folder 50: 1)
    - Edwards, James B. (Box-folder 50: 2)
    - Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain (Box-folder 50: 3)
    - F (Box-folder 50: 4-5)
    - Feulner, Edwin J., Jr. (Box-folder 50: 6)
    - Fielding, Fred F. (Box-folder 50: 7)
    - FitzGerald, Garrett (prime minister of Ireland) (Box-folder 50: 8)
    - Ford, Gerald R. (Box-folder 50: 9)
    - Friedersdorf, Max L. (Box-folder 50: 10)
    - G (Box-folder 50: 11-12)
    - Gandhi, Indira (prime minister of India) (Box-folder 51: 1)
    - Gartland, John C. (Box-folder 51: 2)
    - Garwood, Ellen Clayton (Box-folder 51: 3)
    - Gavin, John (Box-folder 51: 4)
    - Genscher, Hans-Dietrich (West German foreign minister) (Box-folder 51: 5)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 51: 6)
    - Gray, Edwin J. (Box-folder 51: 7)
    - Greenberg, Maxwell E. (Box-folder 51: 8)
    - Grove, David L. (Box-folder 51: 9)
    - H (Box-folder 51: 10-12)
    - Haig, Alexander (Box-folder 51: 13)
    - Hammer, Armand (Box-folder 51: 14)
    - Hannaford, Peter D. (Box-folder 51: 15)
    - Harman, Phillip (Box-folder 51: 16)
    - Hart, Jeffrey (Box-folder 51: 17)
    - Hassan II, King of Morocco (Box-folder 51: 18)
    - Hatch, Orrin G. (Box-folder 51: 19)
    - Heffner, Jane (Box-folder 51: 20)
    - Helms, Jesse (Box-folder 51: 21)
    - Hillings, Patrick J. (Box-folder 52: 1)
    - Hinteregger, Gerald (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 52: 2)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace (Box-folder 52: 3)
    - I (Box-folder 52: 4)
    - Ikle, Fred C. (Box-folder 52: 5)
    - J (Box-folder 52: 6)
    - K (Box-folder 52: 7)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. (Box-folder 52: 8)
    - Kissinger, Henry A. (Box-folder 52: 9)
    - Klestil, Thomas (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 52: 10)
    - Korologos, Tom C. (Box-folder 52: 11)
    - L (Box-folder 52: 12-13)
    - Lagomarsino, Robert J. (Box-folder 52: 14)
    - Lantos, Tom (Box-folder 52: 15)
    - Laxalt, Paul (Box-folder 52: 16)
    - Lewis, Drew (Box-folder 52: 17)
    - Lilienthal, Alfred M. (Box-folder 52: 18)
    - Lillie, Mildred L. (Box-folder 52: 19)
    - Lodge, John Davis (Box-folder 53: 1)
    - Lofton, John (Box-folder 53: 2)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe (Box-folder 53: 3)
    - Luce, Gordon C. (Box-folder 53: 4)
    - M (Box-folder 53: 5-8)
    - Macnow, Alan (Box-folder 54: 1)
    - Majali, Abdul Hadi (Jordanian ambassador) (Box-folder 54: 2)
    - Malitza, Mircea (Romanian ambassador) (Box-folder 54: 3)
    - Marcos, Ferdinand (president of the Philippines) (Box-folder 54: 4)
    - Mayer, Charles T. (Box-folder 54: 5)
    - Meisch, Adrien (Luxembourg ambassador) (Box-folder 54: 6)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II (Box-folder 54: 7)
    - Morris, Robert (Box-folder 54: 8)
    - Mosk, Stanley (Box-folder 54: 9)
    - Mudge, Dirk F. (prime minister of Namibia) (Box-folder 54: 10)
    - N (Box-folder 54: 11)
    - Neill, Kathleen (Box-folder 54: 12-13)
    - Neumann, Robert G. (Box-folder 54: 14)
    - Nitze, Paul H. (Box-folder 54: 15)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 54: 16)
    - Nofziger, Lyn (Box-folder 54: 17)
    - Nunn, Sam (Box-folder 54: 18)
    - O (Box-folder 55: 1)
    - O'Regan, Brendan (Box-folder 55: 2)
    - O'Sullivan Tadhg (Irish ambassador) (Box-folder 55: 3)
    - P (Box-folder 55: 4-6)
    - Pahr, Willibald (Austrian foreign minister) (Box-folder 55: 7)
    - Pfaltzgraff, Robert L., Jr. (Box-folder 55: 8)
    - Price, George Cadle (prime minister of Belize) (Box-folder 55: 9)
    - Q (Box-folder 56: 1)
    - Quayle, Dan (Box-folder 56: 2)
    - Quinn, Arthur Lewis (Box-folder 56: 3)
    - R (Box-folder 56: 4-6)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 56: 7)
    - Regan, Donald T. (Box-folder 56: 8)
    - Richardson, Frank K. (Box-folder 56: 9)
    - Robinson, Gilbert A. (Box-folder 56: 10)
    - Rockefeller, David (Box-folder 56: 11)
    - Rogers, William P. (Box-folder 56: 12)
    - Rostow, Eugene V. (Box-folder 56: 13)
    - Rostow, W. W. (Box-folder 57: 1)
    - Rostropovich, Mstislav (Box-folder 57: 2)
    - Rozek, Edward J. (Box-folder 57: 3)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald (Box-folder 57: 4)
    - Ruppe, Loret Miller (Box-folder 57: 5)
    - Rush, Kenneth (Box-folder 57: 6)
    - Rusk, Dean (Box-folder 57: 7)
    - S (Box-folder 57: 8-10)
    - Sawyer, Thomas E. (Box-folder 57: 11)
    - Schober, Karl Herbert (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 57: 12)
    - Sepulveda, Bernardo (Mexican ambassador) (Box-folder 57: 13)
    - Shakespeare, Frank (Box-folder 58: 1)
    - Shultz, George P. (Box-folder 58: 2)
    - Sinatra, Frank (Box-folder 58: 3)
    - Smith, William French (Box-folder 58: 4)
    - Specter, Arlen (Box-folder 58: 5)
    - Stevens, John Paul (Box-folder 58: 6)
    - Stevens, Ted (Box-folder 58: 7)
    - Sugahara, Kay (Box-folder 58: 8)
    - T (Box-folder 58: 9-10)
    - Takacs, Esteban A. (Argentine ambassador) (Box-folder 58: 11)
    - Tau, M. N. (Lesotho ambassador) (Box-folder 58: 12)
    - Teller, Edward (Box-folder 58: 13)
    - Thapa, Behekh Bahadur (Nepalese ambassador) (Box-folder 58: 14)
    - Thatcher, Margaret (prime minister of Great Britain) (Box-folder 58: 15)
    - Thurmond, Strom (Box-folder 58: 16)
    - U (Box-folder 58: 17)
    - V (Box-folder 58: 18)
    - W (Box-folder 58: 19-20)
    - Walker, June G. (Box-folder 59: 1)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 59: 2)